Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative records, 1963-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Athletics, 1971-1987 (Box 26)
    - Pac 10 (Box 32)
      - 1986 (Box 32)
    - Pan Am Games, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
    - Radio & TV (Box 32)
      - 1973 (Box 32)
      - 1980 (Box 32)
      - 1981 (Box 32)
      - 1984 (Box 32)
      - 1985 (Box 32)
      - 1986 (Box 32)
    - Regional Campus programs, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Soccer (Box 32)
      - 1973 (Box 32)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 32)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 32)
      - 1984 (Box 32)
      - 1986 (Box 32)
    - Swimming (Box 32)
      - 1972-1978 (Box 32)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 32)
    - Televising events, 1970-1981 (Box 32)
    - Television (Box 32)
      - 1973 (Box 32)
      - Contract Basketball, 1972 (Box 32)
      - Coverage of Games (Box 32)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 32)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 32)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 32)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 32)
      - Twelfth Man Club, 1984 (Box 32)
      - Television Coverage of Games, 1972-1973 (Box 32)
    - Tennis (Box 33)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 33)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 33)
    - Ticket Sales, 1972-1979 (Box 33)
    - Track and Field (Box 33)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 33)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 33)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 33)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 33)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 33)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 33)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 33)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 33)
    - Varsity Club (Box 33)
      - 1983 (Box 33)
      - 1984 (Box 33)
      - 1986, (4 folders) (Box 33)
    - Intercollegiate for Women (Box 33)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 33)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 33)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 33)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 33)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 33)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 33)
      - 1978 (Box 33)
      - 1979 (Box 33)
      - 1980 (Box 33)
      - 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 33)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 33)
      - 1985 (Box 33)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Audio Visual Center (Box 33)
    - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 33)
    - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 33)
    - 1976-177, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 34)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 34)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 34)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 34)
    - 1984 (Box 34)
  - Auditorium (Box 34)
    - General (Box 34)
      - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 34)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 34)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 34)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 34)
      - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 34)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 34)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 34)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 34)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 34)
    - Convocations, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Cost Information, 1974 (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 34)
    - Policies, 1975 (Box 34)
    - Proposed Events, 1976 (Box 34)
    - Schedule, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Audubon Society, 1972 (Box 34)
  - Australia, 1971-1974 (Box 34)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises (Box 34)
    - 1971 (Box 34)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 34)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 34)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 34)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 34)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 34)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 34)
  - B, General (Box 34)
    - 1972-1978 (Box 34)
    - 1984 (Box 34)
    - 1983-1986 (Box 34)
    - 1986 (Box 34)
    - 1987 (Box 34)
  - Baccalaureate, 1979-1983 (Box 34)
  - Bacher, Jack, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Bad, 1972-1979 (Box 34)
  - Bak, 1973-1975 (Box 34)
  - Bal, 1979-1981 (Box 34)
  - Ban, 1977-1986 (Box 34)
  - Banda, H. Kamazu of Malawi (Box 34)
    - 1975-1981 (Box 34)
    - visit, 1975 (Box 34)
    - Honorary Degrees - Banda, Hastings Kamuzu, LLD IU Commencement May 3, 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 34)
  - Bar, 1977-1984 (Box 34)
  - Barr, 1979-1984 (Box 34)
  - Bart, 1972-1975 (Box 34)
  - Bas, 1974-1975 (Box 34)
  - Bau, 1972-1979 (Box 34)
  - Be, 1972-1980 (Box 35)
  - Bec, 1971-1978 (Box 35)
  - Bel, 1971-1982 (Box 35)
  - Ben, 1971-1983 (Box 35)
  - Benn, 1971-1975 (Box 35)
  - Ber, 1971-1975 (Box 35)
  - Bern, 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Bi, 1971-1978 (Box 35)
  - Bin, 1971-1977 (Box 35)
  - Bl, 1973-1978 (Box 35)
  - Blak, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Blo, 1971-1983 (Box 35)
  - Bo, 1979-1986 (Box 35)
  - Bon, 1973-1979 (Box 35)
  - Bor, 1977-1982 (Box 35)
  - Bos, 1973-1979 (Box 35)
  - Bow, 1972-1980 (Box 35)
  - Bran, 1974-1983 (Box 35)
  - Bre, 1973-1979 (Box 35)
  - Bren, 1971-1979 (Box 35)
  - Brin, 1976-1979 (Box 35)
  - Bro, 1971-1982 (Box 35)
  - Broo, 1976 (Box 35)
  - Brow, 1973-1981 (Box 35)
  - Bru, 1975-1979 (Box 35)
  - Bu, 1971-1980 (Box 35)
  - Bue, 1971-1982 (Box 35)
  - Bur, 1972-1980 (Box 35)
  - Burn, 1974 (Box 35)
  - But, 1972-1978 (Box 35)
  - Bacchus, 1986 (Box 35)
  - Bacchus Conference, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Ball State University (Box 35)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 35)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 35)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 35)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 35)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 35)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 35)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 35)
    - 1986 (Box 35)
  - Bank Balances (Box 35)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 35)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 35)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 35)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 35)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 35)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 35)
  - Bannon, William G., 1971-1973 (Box 35)
  - Barros, William Paul, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Bartly, Edward R, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Basketball Alumni, 1971-1983 (Box 35)
  - Bayh, Birch, 1971-1978 (Box 35)
  - Beck Chapel, 1967-1983 (Box 35)
  - Bee, 1975 (Box 35)
  - Beechwood Heights, 1984-1987 (Box 35)
  - Bellarmine College-Inauguration, 1974 (Box 35)
  - Benes, Vaclav, 1972 (Box 35)
  - Thomas Hart Benton Murals, 1972-1986 (Box 35)
  - Bex, Brian L. (Box 36)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 36)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 36)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 36)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 36)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 36)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 36)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 36)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 36)
    - 1982 (Box 36)
    - 1983 (Box 36)
    - 1985 (Box 36)
    - 1986 (Box 36)
    - 1987 (Box 36)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1973 (Box 36)
  - Big Ten Business Officers, 1971 (Box 36)
  - Biological Sciences (Box 36)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 36)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 36)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 36)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 36)
  - Biology (Box 36)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 36)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 36)
    - 1985 (Box 36)
    - 1986 (Box 36)
  - Biological sciences, 1986-1987 (Box 36)
  - Biology, Department of President Ryans activity folder, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Bizzari, Larry, 1975 (Box 36)
  - Black Culture Center, 1972 (Box 36)
  - Black History Month, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Black, Glenn A. Laboratory (Box 36)
    - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - 1972-1983 (Box 36)
    - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 36)
  - Black Students (Box 36)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 36)
      General
      Includes: College and the Black Student: NAACP Tract for the Times
    - 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 36)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 36)
    - 1977-1984 (Box 36)
      (Restricted Records Removed)
  - Black Studies (Box 36)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 36)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 36)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 37)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 37)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 37)
  - Bloomington (Box 37)
    - General (Box 37)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 37)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 37)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 37)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 37)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 37)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 37)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 37)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 37)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 37)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 37)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 37)
      - 1982-1984 (Box 37)
      - 1984 (Box 37)
      - 1985 (Box 37)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 37)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 37)
    - Campus Planning, 1979 (Box 37)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 37)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 37)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 37)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 37)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 37)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 37)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 37)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 37)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 37)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 37)
      - 1979 (Box 37)
      - 1984 (Box 37)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 37)
    - City Relations (Box 37)
      - General, 1973 (Box 37)
      - Sewer, 1973-1974 (Box 37)
    - Community Progress Council, 1978-1979 (Box 37)
    - Community Relations, 1964-1976 (Box 37)
    - Business Office Annual Reports (Box 37)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 37)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 37)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 37)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield (Box 37)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 37)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 37)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 37)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 37)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 37)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 37)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 37)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 37)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 37)
    - 1986 (Box 37)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 37)
    - Agenda items, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - September 1971 (Box 38)
    - October 1971 (Box 38)
    - November 1971 (Box 38)
    - December 1971 (Box 38)
    - January 1972 (Box 38)
    - February 1972 (Box 38)
    - Indianapolis, March 1972 (Box 38)
    - Jefferson South-East, April 1972 (Box 38)
    - August 1972 (Box 38)
    - Student Participation in Meetings, August 1972 (Box 38)
    - September 1972 (Box 38)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 39)
    - Student Participation in, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - President Ryan's file, 1973 (Box 39)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 39)
    - August 1974 (Box 39)
    - December 1974 (Box 39)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 39)
    - January 1975 (Box 39)
    - February 1975 (Box 39)
    - March 1975 (Box 39)
    - April 1975 (Box 39)
    - May 1975 (Box 39)
    - June 1975 (Box 39)
    - July 1975 (Box 39)
    - September 1975 (Box 39)
    - October 1975 (Box 40)
    - Agenda, November 1975 (Box 40)
    - November 1975 (Box 40)
    - December 1975 (Box 40)
    - General File, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
    - Trustee File, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - General Trustee Matters, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - January 1976 (Box 40)
    - February 1976 (Box 40)
    - March 1976 (Box 40)
    - April 1976 (Box 40)
    - May 1976 (Box 40)
    - June 1976 (Box 40)
    - Seminar, August 1976; (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - August 1976 (Box 41)
    - September 1976 (Box 41)
    - October 1976 (Box 41)
    - November 1976 (Box 41)
    - December 1976 (Box 41)
    - February 1977 (Box 41)
    - March 1977, (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - April 1977 (Box 41)
    - May 1977, (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - June 1977 (Box 41)
    - July 1977 (Box 41)
    - Trustees Retreat, August 1977 (Box 41)
    - September 1977 (Box 42)
    - October 1977 (Box 42)
    - South Bend, November 1977 (Box 42)
    - December 1977 (Box 42)
    - Special Meeting, December 1977 (Box 42)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 42)
    - National Conference, 1977 (Box 42)
    - February 1978 (Box 42)
    - April 1978 (Box 42)
    - May 1978 (Box 42)
    - June 1978 (Box 42)
    - August 1978, (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - September 1978, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - October 1978 (Box 43)
    - November 1978 (Box 43)
    - December 1978 (Box 43)
    - AGB questionnaire, 1978 (Box 43)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 43)
    - January-March 1979 (Box 43)
    - Meeting on Distinguished Alumni Dinner, January 4, 1979 (Box 43)
    - February 1979 (Box 43)
    - Indianapolis, March 1979 (Box 43)
    - April-June 1979 (Box 43)
    - Special Purchases, Meeting, April 1979 (Box 43)
    - May 1979 (Box 43)
    - Functions of the board, May 1979 (Box 43)
    - Gary, June 1979 (Box 44)
    - June 1979 (Box 44)
    - July-September 1979 (Box 44)
    - Seminar, Aug, 1979; (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - July –, August 1979; (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - August 1979 (Box 44)
    - Presidents Matters, September 1979 (Box 44)
    - October-December 1979 (Box 44)
    - Fort Wayne, October 1979 (Box 44)
    - Richmond, November 1979 (Box 44)
    - Kokomo, December 1979 (Box 44)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 44)
    - Meeting, February 1980 (Box 44)
    - Meeting, Indianapolis, March 1980 (Box 44)
    - South Bend, April 1980 (Box 44)
    - Bloomington, May 1980 (Box 44)
    - June 1980 (Box 45)
    - Union, August 1980 (Box 45)
    - September 1980 (Box 45)
    - October 1980 (Box 45)
    - November 1980 (Box 45)
    - December 1980 (Box 45)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 45)
    - Materials Relevant to the Meetings of Governor Orr, January 1981 (Box 45)
    - IUPUI, February 1981 (Box 45)
    - March 1981 (Box 45)
    - April 1981, (3 folders) (Box 45)
    - May 1981 (Box 46)
    - June 1981 (Box 46)
    - Indianapolis, June 1981 (Box 46)
    - Retreat, August 1981 (Box 46)
    - August 1981 (Box 46)
    - Retreat, September 1981 (Box 46)
    - September 1981 (Box 46)
    - October 1981 (Box 46)
    - Report "Concerning the Public Inspection of Indiana University Accounts of Receipts and Expenditures", November, 1981 (Box 46)
    - December 1981 (Box 46)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 46)
    - Retreat, January 1982 (Box 46)
    - Gary, February 1982 (Box 47)
    - March 1982 (Box 47)
    - Indianapolis, April 1982 (Box 47)
    - May 1982 (Box 47)
    - Fort Wayne, June 1982 (Box 47)
    - Meeting Planning, August 1982 (Box 47)
    - Summer Retreat, August 1982 (Box 47)
    - Indianapolis, August 1982 (Box 47)
    - September 1982 (Box 47)
    - October 1982 (Box 47)
    - Kokomo, November 1982 (Box 47)
    - December 1982 (Box 47)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 47)
    - Winter retreat, February 1983 (Box 48)
    - Indianapolis, March 1983 (Box 48)
    - Executive Committee, April 1983 (Box 48)
    - South Bend, April 1983 (Box 48)
    - May 1983 (Box 48)
    - May 1983, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - June 1983 (Box 48)
    - June 1983 (Box 48)
    - Trustees Summer Retreat, July 1983 (Box 48)
    - Meeting, August 1983 (Box 48)
    - Indianapolis., September 1983 (Box 48)
    - Agenda, September 1983 (Box 48)
    - Meeting, October 1983 (Box 49)
    - National Trustee Workshop, October 1983 (Box 49)
    - IU Southwest, Funding Disparity, November 1983 (Box 49)
    - IUPUI, December 1983 (Box 49)
    - Thank you's, 1983; (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 49)
    - Retreat Meeting, February 1984 (Box 49)
    - Meeting, March 1984 (Box 49)
    - Prudential Building, March 1984 (Box 49)
    - Search and screen procedures, March 1984 (Box 49)
    - April 1984 (Box 49)
    - May 1984 (Box 49)
    - Fiscal Management and Academic Mission Agreement, June 1984 (Box 49)
    - June 1984 (Box 49)
    - July 1984 (Box 49)
    - Proposed IU Project in Malaysia, August 1984 (Box 50)
    - Thank you-Trustees seminar, 1984 (Box 50)
    - President John W. Ryan, The Indianapolis Star, 1984 (Box 50)
    - Seminar Retreat, August 1984; (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Indianapolis., September 1984; (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - October 1984 (Box 50)
    - November 1984, (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Indianapolis, December 1984 (Box 50)
    - Retreat, 1984 (Box 50)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 50)
    - Search and Screen Process (Box 50)
      - August 1984 (Box 50)
      - School of Dentistry, 1984 (Box 50)
      - School of Arts and Sciences, 1984 (Box 50)
      - School of Law, 1984 (Box 50)
      - Herron School of Art, 1984 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees Retreat, January 31-Feburary 2, 1985; (3 folders) (Box 50)
    - "Report of Task Force Reviewing Tuition and Files for Graduate and Professional Schools at IU February, 1985" (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees, Winter Retreat, January 30- February 1, 1985 (Box 51)
    - Winter Retreat Thank You's, 1985 (Box 51)
    - Board of Trustees, New Alban, March 1985 (Box 51)
    - Summer Seminar Meeting, March 1985 (Box 51)
    - IU Board of Trustees meeting, Friday, March 1985; (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - IU Board of Trustees meeting, Friday, 1985; (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Mr. Stoner, June 1985 (Box 51)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, Richmond, June 1985; (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Retreat and Thank You's, August 1985 (Box 51)
    - September 1985, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - October 1985 (Box 51)
    - Southbend, November 1985 (Box 51)
    - December 1985 (Box 52)
    - 1985 (Box 52)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 52)
    - Winter Retreat, January 1986 (Box 52)
    - February 1986 (Box 52)
    - Gary, March 1986 (Box 52)
    - March 1986 (Box 52)
    - April 1986 (Box 52)
    - May 1986 (Box 52)
    - Commencement Figures, 1986 (Box 52)
    - May 1986 (Box 52)
    - June 1986 (Box 52)
    - August 1986 (Box 52)
    - Trustees Retreat, August 1986 (Box 53)
    - October 1986 (Box 53)
    - November 1986 (Box 53)
    - December 1986 (Box 53)
    - 1986 (Box 53)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 53)
    - January 1987 (Box 53)
    - April 1987 (Box 53)
    - June 1987 (Box 53)
    - Salary List-Operating Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 53)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 53)
    - Conflict of Interest disclosure, 1987 (Box 53)
    - 1987 (Box 53)
    - Retreat Thank you's, 1987 (Box 53)
  - Bomb Threats and Threatening Phone Calls (Proposed Policy Concerning), 1971 (Box 54)
  - Bonds (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 54)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 54)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 54)
  - Bookstore (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 54)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 54)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 54)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 54)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 54)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 54)
    - 1984 (Box 54)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 54)
  - Bookstores (IU), 1980-1981 (Box 54)
  - Boone County Contest, Mrs., 1975 (Box 54)
  - Booz, Allen & Hamilton Inc. (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 54)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 54)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 54)
  - Bowman, Sylvia, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Br, 1971-1987 (Box 54)
  - Bradford, Robert Grant, 1971 (Box 54)
  - Bradford Woods (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 54)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 54)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 54)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 54)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 54)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 54)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 54)
  - Breaking Away (Box 54)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 54)
    - undated (Box 54)
  - Bri, 1973-1974 (Box 54)
  - Briscoe Quadrangle, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Brochures, Miscellaneous, 1971-1987 (Box 54)
  - Brown County Playhouse, 1971-1987 (Box 54)
  - Brown, Herbert C., 1979 (Box 54)
  - Bryan Hall (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 54)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 54)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - Open house, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Transferred Reorganization of Offices/Remodeling, 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 54)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 54)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 54)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 54)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 54)
  - Bryan House (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 54)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 54)
  - Budek, Allin, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Budget (Box 54)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 54)
    - Operative, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - Appreciation letters, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 54)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 55)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Appreciation Letter, 1972-1973 (Box 55)
    - Preliminary Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 55)
    - Request Analysis, 1972-1973 (Box 55)
    - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
    - Regional Campuses IUPUI at Fort Wayne, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
    - Hearings, 1974-1975 (Box 55)
    - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 55)
    - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - 1977 (Box 55)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 55)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 55)
    - 1979 (Box 55)
    - Priorities, 1979 (Box 55)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 55)
    - General Fund Summary, 1979-1980 (Box 55)
    - January-June 1980 (Box 55)
    - July-December 1980 (Box 56)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 56)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 56)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 56)
    - Bi-partisan Appeal, 1983 (Box 56)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 56)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 56)
    - State Hearing, 1984 (Box 56)
    - 1985 (Box 56)
    - State Budget Agency Appropriations Hearing, 1986 (Box 56)
    - 1986 (Box 56)
    - 1987 (Box 56)
    - Biennial (Box 56)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 56)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 56)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 56)
      - Capital Appropriation Requests, 1977-1979 (Box 56)
      - IU Special Appropriations Requests, 1977-1979 (Box 56)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 56)
      - Appropriation Requests, 1979-1981 (Box 56)
      - Infractions, 1979-1981 (Box 57)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 57)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 57)
    - Other schools (Box 57)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 57)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Budgetary Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 57)
  - Budget Analysis and Planning Annual Report (Box 57)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 57)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 57)
  - University Budget Office Annual Report (Box 57)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 57)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 57)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 57)
  - Buildings, 1973-1979 (Box 57)
  - Bursar Accounts, 1974 (Box 57)
    (Restricted)
  - Bursar's Office (Box 57)
    - General File (Box 57)
      - 1972-1979 (Box 57)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 57)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 57)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 57)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 57)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 57)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 57)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 57)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 57)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 57)
      - 1985 (Box 57)
      - 1986 (Box 57)
  - Bus, 1971-1987 (Box 57)
  - Business Conference in Indianapolis, 1982 (Box 57)
  - Business Higher Education Forum, 1981 (Box 57)
  - Business Horizons, 1972 (Box 57)
  - Business Manager (Box 57)
    - General, 1978-1983 (Box 57)
    - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 57)
  - Business Placement Office Annual Report (Box 57)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 57)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 57)
  - Business (School of) (Box 57)
    - Annual report, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
    - Annual business conference, 1971-1972 (Box 57)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 57)
    - Annual report, 1971-1972 (Box 57)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 57)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 57)
    - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 57)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 58)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report, 1975-1976; (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 58)
    - Conference, April, 1976 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 58)
    - DBA Luncheon, March 17, 1977 (Box 58)
    - Conference, 1977 (Box 58)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 58)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 58)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 58)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 58)
    - Chief Executive Colloquy, 1981 (Box 58)
    - Annual Conference, 1981 (Box 58)
    - 1983 (Box 58)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 58)
    - 1984 (Box 58)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 58)
    - Search and Screen for Dean, 1982-1984 (Box 58)
    - Conference Luncheon, 1985 (Box 58)
    - 1985 (Box 58)
    - 1986 (Box 59)
    - 1987 (Box 59)
  - C, General (Box 59)
    - 1971-1982 (Box 59)
    - 1983 (Box 59)
    - 1984 (Box 59)
    - 1985 (Box 59)
    - 1986 (Box 59)
  - Cal, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Cam, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Car, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Carm, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Carr, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Cars, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Cas, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Ce, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Ch, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Char, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Chi, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Chr, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Ci, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Cl, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Clar, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Cle, 1971-1987 (Box 59)
  - Co, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Coh, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Col, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Coll, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Com, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Con, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cor, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cos, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cr, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cre, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cro, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cu, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - Cur, 1971-1987 (Box 60)
  - CGR Medical Corp., 1973 (Box 60)
  - Cable Television (Box 60)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 60)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 60)
  - Calendar, 1971-1981 (Box 60)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 60)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 60)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 60)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 60)
    - 1975 (Box 60)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 60)